{"problem": "A BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine and a fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine cost 28 dollars. 3 fruit tarts at Urban Plate cost 3 dollars more than a BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine. A BLT sandwich at Urban Plate costs 14 dollars. Question: how much does a fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine, fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine, fruit tart at Urban Plate are: a BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine and a fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine cost 28 dollars, 3 fruit tarts at Urban Plate cost 3 dollars more than a BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine."}
{"problem": "2 pizzas at Texas BBQ cost 6 dollars less than 2 burgers at Texas BBQ. A pizza at Urban Plate costs 8 dollars. A burger at Texas BBQ and 2 burgers at Urban Plate cost 28 dollars. Question: how much does a burger at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of burger at Texas BBQ, burger at Urban Plate, pizza at Texas BBQ are: a burger at Texas BBQ and 2 burgers at Urban Plate cost 28 dollars, 2 pizzas at Texas BBQ cost 6 dollars less than 2 burgers at Texas BBQ.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of burger at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "2 Cobb salads at Texas BBQ cost 18 dollars more than 2 pies at Taste Good Cuisine. A pie at Texas BBQ costs 8 dollars. A pie at Taste Good Cuisine costs a dollar more than a Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine. Question: how much does a Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pie at Taste Good Cuisine, Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine, Cobb salad at Texas BBQ are: a pie at Taste Good Cuisine costs a dollar more than a Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine, 2 Cobb salads at Texas BBQ cost 18 dollars more than 2 pies at Taste Good Cuisine.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine."}
{"problem": "3 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate cost 15 dollars less than 3 burgers at Urban Plate. A scrambled egg at Urban Plate and a scrambled egg at Mike's Place cost 20 dollars. A burger at Urban Plate costs 8 dollars less than 3 burgers at Mike's Place. Question: how much does a scrambled egg at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of burger at Urban Plate, scrambled egg at Urban Plate, burger at Mike's Place, scrambled egg at Mike's Place are: 3 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate cost 15 dollars less than 3 burgers at Urban Plate, a burger at Urban Plate costs 8 dollars less than 3 burgers at Mike's Place, a scrambled egg at Urban Plate and a scrambled egg at Mike's Place cost 20 dollars.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of scrambled egg at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "A lasagna at Mike's Place costs 7 dollars. 3 lasagnas at Taste Good Cuisine cost 3 dollars less than 2 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine. 3 burgers at Mike's Place cost 9 dollars less than 3 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine. Question: how much does a burger at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of burger at Taste Good Cuisine, burger at Mike's Place, lasagna at Taste Good Cuisine are: 3 burgers at Mike's Place cost 9 dollars less than 3 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine, 3 lasagnas at Taste Good Cuisine cost 3 dollars less than 2 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of burger at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "2 Greek salads at Mike's Place cost 16 dollars more than 2 pieces of fried chicken at Bistro Nice. A piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place costs 15 dollars. 2 pieces of fried chicken at Bistro Nice cost 7 dollars less than 3 Greek salads at Bistro Nice. Question: how much does a Greek salad at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice, Greek salad at Mike's Place, Greek salad at Bistro Nice are: 2 Greek salads at Mike's Place cost 16 dollars more than 2 pieces of fried chicken at Bistro Nice, 2 pieces of fried chicken at Bistro Nice cost 7 dollars less than 3 Greek salads at Bistro Nice.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Greek salad at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "3 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine and a scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine cost 41 dollars. A creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine costs 9 dollars less than 3 cream brulees at Mike's Place. 3 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place cost 13 dollars more than 2 cream brulees at Mike's Place. Question: how much does a creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of creme brulee at Mike's Place, creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine, scrambled egg at Mike's Place, scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine are: a creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine costs 9 dollars less than 3 cream brulees at Mike's Place, 3 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place cost 13 dollars more than 2 cream brulees at Mike's Place, 3 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine and a scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine cost 41 dollars.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine."}
{"problem": "A lasagna at Urban Plate and 3 lasagnas at Taste Good Cuisine cost 23 dollars. A grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine costs 15 dollars less than 3 lasagnas at Urban Plate. A grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate costs 8 dollars. Question: how much does a lasagna at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine, lasagna at Urban Plate, lasagna at Taste Good Cuisine are: a grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine costs 15 dollars less than 3 lasagnas at Urban Plate, a lasagna at Urban Plate and 3 lasagnas at Taste Good Cuisine cost 23 dollars.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of lasagna at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "A piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice and 2 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice cost 41 dollars. A piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice and a BLT sandwich at Urban Plate cost 26 dollars. 3 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice and 3 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate cost 75 dollars. Question: how much does a BLT sandwich at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice, BLT sandwich at Urban Plate, BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice, piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate are: a piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice and a BLT sandwich at Urban Plate cost 26 dollars, a piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice and 2 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice cost 41 dollars, 3 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice and 3 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate cost 75 dollars.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of BLT sandwich at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "2 fruit tarts at Urban Plate cost 18 dollars more than a scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine. A fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate cost 28 dollars. 3 fruit tarts at Urban Plate cost 9 dollars more than 3 fruit tarts at Taste Good Cuisine. Question: how much does a scrambled egg at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine, scrambled egg at Urban Plate, fruit tart at Urban Plate, scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine are: a fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate cost 28 dollars, 3 fruit tarts at Urban Plate cost 9 dollars more than 3 fruit tarts at Taste Good Cuisine, 2 fruit tarts at Urban Plate cost 18 dollars more than a scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of scrambled egg at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "A scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine costs 15 dollars. 2 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate cost 35 dollars less than 3 pies at Taste Good Cuisine. A pie at Urban Plate costs 15 dollars. Question: how much does a pie at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of scrambled egg at Urban Plate, pie at Taste Good Cuisine are: 2 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate cost 35 dollars less than 3 pies at Taste Good Cuisine.\nThere are 2 variables but only 1 linear formula, so we cannot calculate the price of pie at Taste Good Cuisine."}
{"problem": "A pizza at Urban Plate and a piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice cost 14 dollars. 3 pizzas at Urban Plate cost 12 dollars more than a pizza at Bistro Nice. A piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate costs 12 dollars. Question: how much does a pizza at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pizza at Bistro Nice, pizza at Urban Plate, piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice are: 3 pizzas at Urban Plate cost 12 dollars more than a pizza at Bistro Nice, a pizza at Urban Plate and a piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice cost 14 dollars.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of pizza at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "A burger at Texas BBQ costs 2 dollars more than a pie at Urban Plate. A pie at Texas BBQ costs a dollar more than a burger at Texas BBQ. 3 pies at Texas BBQ and 3 burgers at Urban Plate cost 63 dollars. Question: how much does a pie at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of burger at Texas BBQ, pie at Urban Plate, pie at Texas BBQ, burger at Urban Plate are: a burger at Texas BBQ costs 2 dollars more than a pie at Urban Plate, a pie at Texas BBQ costs a dollar more than a burger at Texas BBQ, 3 pies at Texas BBQ and 3 burgers at Urban Plate cost 63 dollars.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of pie at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "A pizza at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 lasagnas at Taste Good Cuisine cost 48 dollars. A lasagna at Urban Plate costs 6 dollars. 3 lasagnas at Urban Plate and 3 pizzas at Urban Plate cost 63 dollars. Question: how much does a lasagna at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pizza at Taste Good Cuisine, lasagna at Taste Good Cuisine are: a pizza at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 lasagnas at Taste Good Cuisine cost 48 dollars.\nThere are 2 variables but only 1 linear formula, so we cannot calculate the price of lasagna at Taste Good Cuisine."}
{"problem": "A BLT sandwich at Mike's Place costs 8 dollars less than a BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ. 3 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place and 3 burgers at Texas BBQ cost 66 dollars. A BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ and 3 burgers at Mike's Place cost 42 dollars. Question: how much does a BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of BLT sandwich at Mike's Place, BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ, burger at Texas BBQ, burger at Mike's Place are: a BLT sandwich at Mike's Place costs 8 dollars less than a BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ, 3 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place and 3 burgers at Texas BBQ cost 66 dollars, a BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ and 3 burgers at Mike's Place cost 42 dollars.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "3 burgers at Bistro Nice and a Cobb salad at Bistro Nice cost 41 dollars. A burger at Mike's Place costs 15 dollars. 3 Cobb salads at Mike's Place cost 12 dollars more than 3 burgers at Bistro Nice. Question: how much does a burger at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Cobb salad at Mike's Place, burger at Bistro Nice, Cobb salad at Bistro Nice are: 3 Cobb salads at Mike's Place cost 12 dollars more than 3 burgers at Bistro Nice, 3 burgers at Bistro Nice and a Cobb salad at Bistro Nice cost 41 dollars.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of burger at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "The price of a BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice is the same as that of a piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine. 2 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice cost 48 dollars. A BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice and 2 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 41 dollars. Question: how much does a BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine, BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice, piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice, BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine are: the price of a BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice is the same as that of a piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine, 2 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice cost 48 dollars, a BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice and 2 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 41 dollars.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "2 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ and 2 pieces of fried chicken at Bistro Nice cost 38 dollars. A fruit tart at Bistro Nice costs 7 dollars less than 2 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ. 2 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ and a piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ cost 19 dollars. Question: how much does a piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of fruit tart at Texas BBQ, piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ, piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice, fruit tart at Bistro Nice are: 2 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ and a piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ cost 19 dollars, 2 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ and 2 pieces of fried chicken at Bistro Nice cost 38 dollars, a fruit tart at Bistro Nice costs 7 dollars less than 2 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of piece of fried chicken at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "A lasagna at Mike's Place costs 17 dollars less than 2 fruit tarts at Mike's Place. 2 fruit tarts at Mike's Place and a fruit tart at Texas BBQ cost 32 dollars. A fruit tart at Mike's Place and 2 lasagnas at Texas BBQ cost 25 dollars. Question: how much does a lasagna at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of fruit tart at Mike's Place, lasagna at Mike's Place, lasagna at Texas BBQ, fruit tart at Texas BBQ are: a lasagna at Mike's Place costs 17 dollars less than 2 fruit tarts at Mike's Place, a fruit tart at Mike's Place and 2 lasagnas at Texas BBQ cost 25 dollars, 2 fruit tarts at Mike's Place and a fruit tart at Texas BBQ cost 32 dollars.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of lasagna at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "A Caesar salad at Bistro Nice costs a dollar less than a burger at Bistro Nice. A burger at Bistro Nice costs 35 dollars less than 3 burgers at Mike's Place. 3 Caesar salads at Mike's Place cost 9 dollars less than 3 Caesar salads at Bistro Nice. Question: how much does a Caesar salad at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Caesar salad at Mike's Place, Caesar salad at Bistro Nice, burger at Bistro Nice, burger at Mike's Place are: 3 Caesar salads at Mike's Place cost 9 dollars less than 3 Caesar salads at Bistro Nice, a Caesar salad at Bistro Nice costs a dollar less than a burger at Bistro Nice, a burger at Bistro Nice costs 35 dollars less than 3 burgers at Mike's Place.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Caesar salad at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "3 fruit tarts at Urban Plate cost 10 dollars more than a grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ. 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate and 3 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ cost 42 dollars. 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 3 dollars more than 3 fruit tarts at Urban Plate. Question: how much does a fruit tart at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ, fruit tart at Urban Plate, grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate, fruit tart at Texas BBQ are: 3 fruit tarts at Urban Plate cost 10 dollars more than a grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ, 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 3 dollars more than 3 fruit tarts at Urban Plate, 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate and 3 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ cost 42 dollars.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of fruit tart at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "3 lasagnas at Taste Good Cuisine and a lasagna at Mike's Place cost 56 dollars. 2 lasagnas at Mike's Place cost 8 dollars less than 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine. 3 lasagnas at Mike's Place and 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 66 dollars. Question: how much does a lasagna at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of lasagna at Taste Good Cuisine, lasagna at Mike's Place, grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine, grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place are: 3 lasagnas at Taste Good Cuisine and a lasagna at Mike's Place cost 56 dollars, 2 lasagnas at Mike's Place cost 8 dollars less than 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine, 3 lasagnas at Mike's Place and 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 66 dollars.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of lasagna at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "3 BLT sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 21 dollars less than 3 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine. A piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine costs 24 dollars less than 3 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ. 2 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 18 dollars more than a piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine. Question: how much does a piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ, piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine, BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine, BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ are: a piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine costs 24 dollars less than 3 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ, 2 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 18 dollars more than a piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine, 3 BLT sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 21 dollars less than 3 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine."}
{"problem": "3 cream brulees at Bistro Nice cost 18 dollars less than 3 burgers at Mike's Place. 2 burgers at Mike's Place and 2 cream brulees at Mike's Place cost 40 dollars. 3 cream brulees at Bistro Nice and 3 burgers at Bistro Nice cost 60 dollars. Question: how much does a burger at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of creme brulee at Bistro Nice, burger at Bistro Nice, burger at Mike's Place, creme brulee at Mike's Place are: 3 cream brulees at Bistro Nice and 3 burgers at Bistro Nice cost 60 dollars, 3 cream brulees at Bistro Nice cost 18 dollars less than 3 burgers at Mike's Place, 2 burgers at Mike's Place and 2 cream brulees at Mike's Place cost 40 dollars.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of burger at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "3 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine cost 3 dollars less than 2 Greek salads at Texas BBQ. A Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine costs a dollar more than 2 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine. 2 burgers at Texas BBQ cost 3 dollars more than 3 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine. Question: how much does a burger at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Greek salad at Texas BBQ, burger at Taste Good Cuisine, burger at Texas BBQ, Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine are: 3 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine cost 3 dollars less than 2 Greek salads at Texas BBQ, 2 burgers at Texas BBQ cost 3 dollars more than 3 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine, a Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine costs a dollar more than 2 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of burger at Taste Good Cuisine."}
{"problem": "A scrambled egg at Bistro Nice and a piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place cost 21 dollars. 2 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice cost 6 dollars more than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice. A scrambled egg at Mike's Place costs 6 dollars. Question: how much does a scrambled egg at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice, scrambled egg at Bistro Nice, piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place are: 2 scrambled eggs at Bistro Nice cost 6 dollars more than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice, a scrambled egg at Bistro Nice and a piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place cost 21 dollars.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of scrambled egg at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "A Cobb salad at Bistro Nice costs 11 dollars. A pie at Bistro Nice costs 14 dollars less than 2 Cobb salads at Urban Plate. 3 pies at Urban Plate cost a dollar less than 2 pies at Bistro Nice. Question: how much does a pie at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pie at Urban Plate, pie at Bistro Nice, Cobb salad at Urban Plate are: 3 pies at Urban Plate cost a dollar less than 2 pies at Bistro Nice, a pie at Bistro Nice costs 14 dollars less than 2 Cobb salads at Urban Plate.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of pie at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "3 pizzas at Bistro Nice cost 18 dollars more than a burger at Bistro Nice. 3 pizzas at Urban Plate cost 12 dollars more than 3 pizzas at Bistro Nice. A burger at Urban Plate costs 12 dollars less than 2 pizzas at Bistro Nice. Question: how much does a burger at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pizza at Bistro Nice, burger at Urban Plate, burger at Bistro Nice, pizza at Urban Plate are: a burger at Urban Plate costs 12 dollars less than 2 pizzas at Bistro Nice, 3 pizzas at Bistro Nice cost 18 dollars more than a burger at Bistro Nice, 3 pizzas at Urban Plate cost 12 dollars more than 3 pizzas at Bistro Nice.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of burger at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "3 pizzas at Bistro Nice and 3 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice cost 66 dollars. 2 pizzas at Texas BBQ cost 4 dollars more than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ. A pizza at Texas BBQ and 2 pizzas at Bistro Nice cost 34 dollars. Question: how much does a piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pizza at Texas BBQ, piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ, pizza at Bistro Nice, piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice are: 2 pizzas at Texas BBQ cost 4 dollars more than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ, a pizza at Texas BBQ and 2 pizzas at Bistro Nice cost 34 dollars, 3 pizzas at Bistro Nice and 3 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice cost 66 dollars.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "2 Caesar salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 5 dollars less than 3 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine. A creme brulee at Urban Plate costs 12 dollars. A Caesar salad at Urban Plate costs a dollar less than 2 Caesar salads at Taste Good Cuisine. Question: how much does a creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Caesar salad at Taste Good Cuisine, creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine, Caesar salad at Urban Plate are: 2 Caesar salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 5 dollars less than 3 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine, a Caesar salad at Urban Plate costs a dollar less than 2 Caesar salads at Taste Good Cuisine.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine."}
{"problem": "A lasagna at Mike's Place costs 15 dollars. A Cobb salad at Mike's Place costs 14 dollars. 2 lasagnas at Bistro Nice cost 12 dollars less than 3 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice. Question: how much does a lasagna at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Cobb salad at Bistro Nice, lasagna at Bistro Nice are: 2 lasagnas at Bistro Nice cost 12 dollars less than 3 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice.\nThere are 2 variables but only 1 linear formula, so we cannot calculate the price of lasagna at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "A piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine costs 17 dollars less than 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine. 2 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate cost 19 dollars less than 3 pieces of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine. A piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate and 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 20 dollars. Question: how much does a grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine, grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine, piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate, grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate are: a piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine costs 17 dollars less than 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine, 2 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate cost 19 dollars less than 3 pieces of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine, a piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate and 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 20 dollars.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine."}
{"problem": "2 pizzas at Texas BBQ cost 6 dollars more than a pie at Urban Plate. A pizza at Urban Plate costs 16 dollars less than 2 pies at Texas BBQ. 2 pies at Urban Plate cost 16 dollars more than a pizza at Urban Plate. Question: how much does a pie at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pizza at Texas BBQ, pie at Urban Plate, pizza at Urban Plate, pie at Texas BBQ are: 2 pizzas at Texas BBQ cost 6 dollars more than a pie at Urban Plate, 2 pies at Urban Plate cost 16 dollars more than a pizza at Urban Plate, a pizza at Urban Plate costs 16 dollars less than 2 pies at Texas BBQ.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of pie at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "2 Caesar salads at Urban Plate and a piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate cost 37 dollars. 2 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate cost 18 dollars more than a piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place. 3 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place cost 12 dollars more than a Caesar salad at Mike's Place. Question: how much does a piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Caesar salad at Urban Plate, piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate, piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place, Caesar salad at Mike's Place are: 2 Caesar salads at Urban Plate and a piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate cost 37 dollars, 2 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate cost 18 dollars more than a piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place, 3 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place cost 12 dollars more than a Caesar salad at Mike's Place.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "A fruit tart at Texas BBQ costs 9 dollars less than 2 pies at Mike's Place. A fruit tart at Mike's Place costs a dollar less than a fruit tart at Texas BBQ. 3 pies at Mike's Place and 3 pies at Texas BBQ cost 45 dollars. Question: how much does a fruit tart at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pie at Mike's Place, fruit tart at Texas BBQ, pie at Texas BBQ, fruit tart at Mike's Place are: a fruit tart at Texas BBQ costs 9 dollars less than 2 pies at Mike's Place, 3 pies at Mike's Place and 3 pies at Texas BBQ cost 45 dollars, a fruit tart at Mike's Place costs a dollar less than a fruit tart at Texas BBQ.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of fruit tart at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "A burger at Urban Plate costs 14 dollars less than 3 Cobb salads at Mike's Place. A burger at Mike's Place costs 7 dollars. A Cobb salad at Mike's Place costs 6 dollars less than 3 Cobb salads at Urban Plate. Question: how much does a Cobb salad at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Cobb salad at Mike's Place, Cobb salad at Urban Plate, burger at Urban Plate are: a Cobb salad at Mike's Place costs 6 dollars less than 3 Cobb salads at Urban Plate, a burger at Urban Plate costs 14 dollars less than 3 Cobb salads at Mike's Place.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Cobb salad at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "3 pieces of cheese cake at Mike's Place and a pizza at Taste Good Cuisine cost 33 dollars. A pizza at Taste Good Cuisine costs 12 dollars less than 3 pizzas at Mike's Place. 3 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine cost 27 dollars more than a piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place. Question: how much does a piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place, piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine, pizza at Taste Good Cuisine, pizza at Mike's Place are: 3 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine cost 27 dollars more than a piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place, 3 pieces of cheese cake at Mike's Place and a pizza at Taste Good Cuisine cost 33 dollars, a pizza at Taste Good Cuisine costs 12 dollars less than 3 pizzas at Mike's Place.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine."}
{"problem": "A piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ cost 54 dollars. A lasagna at Taste Good Cuisine costs 11 dollars. 3 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 lasagnas at Texas BBQ cost 63 dollars. Question: how much does a lasagna at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine, lasagna at Texas BBQ, piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ are: 3 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 lasagnas at Texas BBQ cost 63 dollars, a piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ cost 54 dollars.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of lasagna at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "2 Greek salads at Bistro Nice cost 18 dollars less than 3 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate. A Greek salad at Urban Plate costs 12 dollars. 3 Greek salads at Bistro Nice and 2 pieces of fried chicken at Bistro Nice cost 54 dollars. Question: how much does a piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Greek salad at Bistro Nice, piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate, piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice are: 2 Greek salads at Bistro Nice cost 18 dollars less than 3 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate, 3 Greek salads at Bistro Nice and 2 pieces of fried chicken at Bistro Nice cost 54 dollars.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "2 Cobb salads at Mike's Place cost 8 dollars more than a pie at Bistro Nice. 2 pies at Mike's Place cost 11 dollars less than 3 Cobb salads at Mike's Place. 2 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice cost 2 dollars more than 2 pies at Bistro Nice. Question: how much does a pie at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Cobb salad at Mike's Place, pie at Bistro Nice, pie at Mike's Place, Cobb salad at Bistro Nice are: 2 Cobb salads at Mike's Place cost 8 dollars more than a pie at Bistro Nice, 2 pies at Mike's Place cost 11 dollars less than 3 Cobb salads at Mike's Place, 2 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice cost 2 dollars more than 2 pies at Bistro Nice.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of pie at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "A lasagna at Texas BBQ costs 15 dollars. 2 lasagnas at Taste Good Cuisine cost 3 dollars less than 3 Caesar salads at Taste Good Cuisine. A lasagna at Taste Good Cuisine costs 2 dollars less than a Caesar salad at Texas BBQ. Question: how much does a lasagna at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Caesar salad at Taste Good Cuisine, lasagna at Taste Good Cuisine, Caesar salad at Texas BBQ are: 2 lasagnas at Taste Good Cuisine cost 3 dollars less than 3 Caesar salads at Taste Good Cuisine, a lasagna at Taste Good Cuisine costs 2 dollars less than a Caesar salad at Texas BBQ.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of lasagna at Taste Good Cuisine."}
{"problem": "2 lasagnas at Bistro Nice cost 8 dollars more than 2 pies at Bistro Nice. A pie at Mike's Place costs 10 dollars. 2 lasagnas at Mike's Place cost 2 dollars less than 2 pies at Bistro Nice. Question: how much does a lasagna at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pie at Bistro Nice, lasagna at Mike's Place, lasagna at Bistro Nice are: 2 lasagnas at Mike's Place cost 2 dollars less than 2 pies at Bistro Nice, 2 lasagnas at Bistro Nice cost 8 dollars more than 2 pies at Bistro Nice.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of lasagna at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 19 dollars less than 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine. 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 3 dollars less than 3 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine. A BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ costs 12 dollars. Question: how much does a grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine, grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ, BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine are: 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 19 dollars less than 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine, 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 3 dollars less than 3 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "A pizza at Bistro Nice and a BLT sandwich at Mike's Place cost 16 dollars. 2 pizzas at Mike's Place cost 3 dollars less than a BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice. A BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 5 dollars less than 2 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place. Question: how much does a BLT sandwich at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pizza at Bistro Nice, BLT sandwich at Mike's Place, BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice, pizza at Mike's Place are: a pizza at Bistro Nice and a BLT sandwich at Mike's Place cost 16 dollars, a BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice costs 5 dollars less than 2 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place, 2 pizzas at Mike's Place cost 3 dollars less than a BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of BLT sandwich at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "A pizza at Texas BBQ costs 13 dollars. 2 pizzas at Urban Plate cost 12 dollars more than 2 burgers at Urban Plate. 2 pizzas at Urban Plate cost 21 dollars more than a burger at Texas BBQ. Question: how much does a pizza at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of burger at Urban Plate, pizza at Urban Plate, burger at Texas BBQ are: 2 pizzas at Urban Plate cost 12 dollars more than 2 burgers at Urban Plate, 2 pizzas at Urban Plate cost 21 dollars more than a burger at Texas BBQ.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of pizza at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "A Greek salad at Texas BBQ and 3 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ cost 49 dollars. 3 Greek salads at Texas BBQ and 2 Greek salads at Urban Plate cost 56 dollars. 2 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ cost 15 dollars more than a piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate. Question: how much does a piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Greek salad at Texas BBQ, piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ, Greek salad at Urban Plate, piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate are: a Greek salad at Texas BBQ and 3 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ cost 49 dollars, 3 Greek salads at Texas BBQ and 2 Greek salads at Urban Plate cost 56 dollars, 2 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ cost 15 dollars more than a piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "3 cream brulees at Texas BBQ and 2 cream brulees at Urban Plate cost 67 dollars. A scrambled egg at Urban Plate costs 6 dollars. 3 cream brulees at Texas BBQ cost 29 dollars more than a scrambled egg at Texas BBQ. Question: how much does a creme brulee at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of creme brulee at Texas BBQ, creme brulee at Urban Plate, scrambled egg at Texas BBQ are: 3 cream brulees at Texas BBQ and 2 cream brulees at Urban Plate cost 67 dollars, 3 cream brulees at Texas BBQ cost 29 dollars more than a scrambled egg at Texas BBQ.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of creme brulee at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "A BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine costs 3 dollars more than a creme brulee at Texas BBQ. A BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ costs 15 dollars less than 3 cream brulees at Texas BBQ. 3 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine cost 61 dollars. Question: how much does a BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of creme brulee at Texas BBQ, BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ, BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine, creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine are: a BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ costs 15 dollars less than 3 cream brulees at Texas BBQ, a BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine costs 3 dollars more than a creme brulee at Texas BBQ, 3 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine cost 61 dollars.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "A creme brulee at Texas BBQ costs 25 dollars less than 3 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine. 3 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ and 3 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine cost 30 dollars. 2 cream brulees at Texas BBQ and 2 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ cost 20 dollars. Question: how much does a scrambled egg at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of creme brulee at Texas BBQ, scrambled egg at Texas BBQ, scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine, creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine are: 2 cream brulees at Texas BBQ and 2 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ cost 20 dollars, a creme brulee at Texas BBQ costs 25 dollars less than 3 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine, 3 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ and 3 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine cost 30 dollars.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of scrambled egg at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "A lasagna at Texas BBQ costs 12 dollars. 3 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine and a lasagna at Taste Good Cuisine cost 45 dollars. 2 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ cost 6 dollars more than 2 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine. Question: how much does a scrambled egg at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine, scrambled egg at Texas BBQ, lasagna at Taste Good Cuisine are: 2 scrambled eggs at Texas BBQ cost 6 dollars more than 2 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine, 3 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine and a lasagna at Taste Good Cuisine cost 45 dollars.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of scrambled egg at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "A pie at Mike's Place costs 16 dollars less than 2 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place. 2 pies at Urban Plate cost 9 dollars less than 3 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place. 2 pies at Urban Plate and 2 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate cost 40 dollars. Question: how much does a pie at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of scrambled egg at Mike's Place, pie at Urban Plate, pie at Mike's Place, scrambled egg at Urban Plate are: 2 pies at Urban Plate cost 9 dollars less than 3 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place, a pie at Mike's Place costs 16 dollars less than 2 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place, 2 pies at Urban Plate and 2 scrambled eggs at Urban Plate cost 40 dollars.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of pie at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "A BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ costs 2 dollars less than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ. A piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ costs 37 dollars less than 3 BLT sandwiches at Urban Plate. 3 BLT sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 36 dollars more than a piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate. Question: how much does a piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of BLT sandwich at Urban Plate, piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ, piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate, BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ are: a piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ costs 37 dollars less than 3 BLT sandwiches at Urban Plate, 3 BLT sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 36 dollars more than a piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate, a BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ costs 2 dollars less than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "2 fruit tarts at Mike's Place and a fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine cost 39 dollars. 3 fruit tarts at Mike's Place and 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 65 dollars. 2 fruit tarts at Mike's Place cost 6 dollars more than 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine. Question: how much does a grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of fruit tart at Mike's Place, grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine, grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place, fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine are: 2 fruit tarts at Mike's Place cost 6 dollars more than 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine, 3 fruit tarts at Mike's Place and 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 65 dollars, 2 fruit tarts at Mike's Place and a fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine cost 39 dollars.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine."}
{"problem": "3 Cobb salads at Mike's Place cost 30 dollars more than a creme brulee at Urban Plate. 3 cream brulees at Mike's Place and 2 Cobb salads at Urban Plate cost 56 dollars. 3 cream brulees at Mike's Place cost 21 dollars more than a creme brulee at Urban Plate. Question: how much does a Cobb salad at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of creme brulee at Mike's Place, Cobb salad at Urban Plate, creme brulee at Urban Plate, Cobb salad at Mike's Place are: 3 cream brulees at Mike's Place and 2 Cobb salads at Urban Plate cost 56 dollars, 3 cream brulees at Mike's Place cost 21 dollars more than a creme brulee at Urban Plate, 3 Cobb salads at Mike's Place cost 30 dollars more than a creme brulee at Urban Plate.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Cobb salad at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "A fruit tart at Texas BBQ costs 12 dollars. 3 BLT sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 6 dollars more than a fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine. 2 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 2 dollars more than 2 BLT sandwiches at Texas BBQ. Question: how much does a fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ, fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine, BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine are: 3 BLT sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 6 dollars more than a fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine, 2 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 2 dollars more than 2 BLT sandwiches at Texas BBQ.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine."}
{"problem": "2 pies at Urban Plate cost 2 dollars less than a scrambled egg at Bistro Nice. The price of a scrambled egg at Urban Plate is the same as that of 2 pies at Urban Plate. 3 pies at Bistro Nice cost 14 dollars more than 2 pies at Urban Plate. Question: how much does a scrambled egg at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pie at Urban Plate, scrambled egg at Urban Plate, pie at Bistro Nice, scrambled egg at Bistro Nice are: the price of a scrambled egg at Urban Plate is the same as that of 2 pies at Urban Plate, 3 pies at Bistro Nice cost 14 dollars more than 2 pies at Urban Plate, 2 pies at Urban Plate cost 2 dollars less than a scrambled egg at Bistro Nice.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of scrambled egg at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "A scrambled egg at Texas BBQ costs 14 dollars. A Cobb salad at Texas BBQ costs 22 dollars less than 3 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine. A Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine costs 7 dollars. Question: how much does a Cobb salad at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine, Cobb salad at Texas BBQ are: a Cobb salad at Texas BBQ costs 22 dollars less than 3 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine.\nThere are 2 variables but only 1 linear formula, so we cannot calculate the price of Cobb salad at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "A creme brulee at Mike's Place costs 4 dollars more than a lasagna at Mike's Place. A lasagna at Mike's Place costs 12 dollars less than 3 lasagnas at Bistro Nice. A creme brulee at Bistro Nice costs 6 dollars. Question: how much does a lasagna at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of creme brulee at Mike's Place, lasagna at Mike's Place, lasagna at Bistro Nice are: a creme brulee at Mike's Place costs 4 dollars more than a lasagna at Mike's Place, a lasagna at Mike's Place costs 12 dollars less than 3 lasagnas at Bistro Nice.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of lasagna at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "A fruit tart at Mike's Place costs 13 dollars. 2 fruit tarts at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 Greek salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 60 dollars. A Greek salad at Mike's Place costs 26 dollars less than 3 Greek salads at Taste Good Cuisine. Question: how much does a Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine, Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine, Greek salad at Mike's Place are: 2 fruit tarts at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 Greek salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 60 dollars, a Greek salad at Mike's Place costs 26 dollars less than 3 Greek salads at Taste Good Cuisine.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine."}
{"problem": "A pizza at Taste Good Cuisine costs 6 dollars more than a pizza at Texas BBQ. The price of 3 pizzas at Texas BBQ is the same as that of 3 Caesar salads at Texas BBQ. 3 Caesar salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 6 dollars less than 3 pizzas at Taste Good Cuisine. Question: how much does a pizza at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pizza at Taste Good Cuisine, pizza at Texas BBQ, Caesar salad at Taste Good Cuisine, Caesar salad at Texas BBQ are: a pizza at Taste Good Cuisine costs 6 dollars more than a pizza at Texas BBQ, 3 Caesar salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 6 dollars less than 3 pizzas at Taste Good Cuisine, the price of 3 pizzas at Texas BBQ is the same as that of 3 Caesar salads at Texas BBQ.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of pizza at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "3 cream brulees at Urban Plate cost 13 dollars more than 2 cream brulees at Texas BBQ. 2 Cobb salads at Texas BBQ cost 2 dollars more than 2 cream brulees at Urban Plate. 2 Cobb salads at Texas BBQ and 3 Cobb salads at Urban Plate cost 48 dollars. Question: how much does a Cobb salad at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Cobb salad at Texas BBQ, Cobb salad at Urban Plate, creme brulee at Urban Plate, creme brulee at Texas BBQ are: 2 Cobb salads at Texas BBQ and 3 Cobb salads at Urban Plate cost 48 dollars, 2 Cobb salads at Texas BBQ cost 2 dollars more than 2 cream brulees at Urban Plate, 3 cream brulees at Urban Plate cost 13 dollars more than 2 cream brulees at Texas BBQ.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Cobb salad at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "3 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine cost 8 dollars more than a Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine. 2 Cobb salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 11 dollars more than 3 Cobb salads at Urban Plate. 3 Cobb salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 25 dollars more than a piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate. Question: how much does a Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine, Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine, Cobb salad at Urban Plate, piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate are: 3 pieces of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine cost 8 dollars more than a Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine, 2 Cobb salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 11 dollars more than 3 Cobb salads at Urban Plate, 3 Cobb salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 25 dollars more than a piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine."}
{"problem": "3 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place cost 8 dollars more than a lasagna at Mike's Place. A piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine costs 13 dollars. The price of 3 lasagnas at Taste Good Cuisine is the same as that of 3 lasagnas at Mike's Place. Question: how much does a lasagna at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place, lasagna at Mike's Place, lasagna at Taste Good Cuisine are: 3 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place cost 8 dollars more than a lasagna at Mike's Place, the price of 3 lasagnas at Taste Good Cuisine is the same as that of 3 lasagnas at Mike's Place.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of lasagna at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "A Greek salad at Mike's Place costs 5 dollars less than a Caesar salad at Mike's Place. 3 Greek salads at Urban Plate and 3 Caesar salads at Urban Plate cost 42 dollars. 3 Greek salads at Mike's Place and a Greek salad at Urban Plate cost 22 dollars. Question: how much does a Greek salad at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Caesar salad at Mike's Place, Greek salad at Mike's Place, Greek salad at Urban Plate, Caesar salad at Urban Plate are: a Greek salad at Mike's Place costs 5 dollars less than a Caesar salad at Mike's Place, 3 Greek salads at Mike's Place and a Greek salad at Urban Plate cost 22 dollars, 3 Greek salads at Urban Plate and 3 Caesar salads at Urban Plate cost 42 dollars.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Greek salad at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "A grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ costs 7 dollars. 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 4 dollars more than 2 Greek salads at Mike's Place. A Greek salad at Texas BBQ costs 14 dollars. Question: how much does a grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Greek salad at Mike's Place, grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place are: 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 4 dollars more than 2 Greek salads at Mike's Place.\nThere are 2 variables but only 1 linear formula, so we cannot calculate the price of grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "3 pies at Urban Plate and a BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ cost 42 dollars. A pie at Texas BBQ costs 3 dollars less than a pie at Urban Plate. 3 BLT sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 15 dollars more than 3 pies at Texas BBQ. Question: how much does a pie at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of BLT sandwich at Urban Plate, pie at Texas BBQ, pie at Urban Plate, BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ are: 3 BLT sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 15 dollars more than 3 pies at Texas BBQ, a pie at Texas BBQ costs 3 dollars less than a pie at Urban Plate, 3 pies at Urban Plate and a BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ cost 42 dollars.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of pie at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "3 cream brulees at Urban Plate cost 29 dollars more than a BLT sandwich at Urban Plate. 2 cream brulees at Urban Plate cost 17 dollars more than a creme brulee at Bistro Nice. 3 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice cost 3 dollars less than 3 cream brulees at Urban Plate. Question: how much does a BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of creme brulee at Urban Plate, BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice, creme brulee at Bistro Nice, BLT sandwich at Urban Plate are: 3 BLT sandwiches at Bistro Nice cost 3 dollars less than 3 cream brulees at Urban Plate, 2 cream brulees at Urban Plate cost 17 dollars more than a creme brulee at Bistro Nice, 3 cream brulees at Urban Plate cost 29 dollars more than a BLT sandwich at Urban Plate.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of BLT sandwich at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "A pie at Taste Good Cuisine costs 5 dollars. 2 pies at Taste Good Cuisine and a lasagna at Taste Good Cuisine cost 20 dollars. 3 pies at Mike's Place and 2 lasagnas at Mike's Place cost 40 dollars. Question: how much does a lasagna at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pie at Mike's Place, lasagna at Mike's Place are: 3 pies at Mike's Place and 2 lasagnas at Mike's Place cost 40 dollars.\nThere are 2 variables but only 1 linear formula, so we cannot calculate the price of lasagna at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "3 pies at Taste Good Cuisine and a BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine cost 24 dollars. A pie at Urban Plate costs 2 dollars less than a BLT sandwich at Urban Plate. 2 pies at Urban Plate cost 14 dollars more than 2 pies at Taste Good Cuisine. Question: how much does a pie at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pie at Taste Good Cuisine, pie at Urban Plate, BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine, BLT sandwich at Urban Plate are: 2 pies at Urban Plate cost 14 dollars more than 2 pies at Taste Good Cuisine, 3 pies at Taste Good Cuisine and a BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine cost 24 dollars, a pie at Urban Plate costs 2 dollars less than a BLT sandwich at Urban Plate.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of pie at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice cost 17 dollars less than 3 cream brulees at Bistro Nice. 3 cream brulees at Urban Plate and 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice cost 70 dollars. 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice cost 16 dollars more than a piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate. Question: how much does a piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of creme brulee at Urban Plate, piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice, piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate, creme brulee at Bistro Nice are: 3 cream brulees at Urban Plate and 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice cost 70 dollars, 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice cost 16 dollars more than a piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate, 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice cost 17 dollars less than 3 cream brulees at Bistro Nice.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "The price of 3 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place is the same as that of 2 pizzas at Taste Good Cuisine. 3 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 pizzas at Mike's Place cost 63 dollars. 3 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 3 dollars more than a BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine. Question: how much does a BLT sandwich at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pizza at Taste Good Cuisine, BLT sandwich at Mike's Place, BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine, pizza at Mike's Place are: the price of 3 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place is the same as that of 2 pizzas at Taste Good Cuisine, 3 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 3 dollars more than a BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine, 3 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 pizzas at Mike's Place cost 63 dollars.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of BLT sandwich at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "2 Caesar salads at Urban Plate cost 6 dollars less than 2 pizzas at Urban Plate. 2 Caesar salads at Urban Plate cost 14 dollars less than 2 Caesar salads at Bistro Nice. 3 pizzas at Urban Plate and 3 pizzas at Bistro Nice cost 60 dollars. Question: how much does a pizza at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Caesar salad at Urban Plate, pizza at Urban Plate, Caesar salad at Bistro Nice, pizza at Bistro Nice are: 2 Caesar salads at Urban Plate cost 6 dollars less than 2 pizzas at Urban Plate, 2 Caesar salads at Urban Plate cost 14 dollars less than 2 Caesar salads at Bistro Nice, 3 pizzas at Urban Plate and 3 pizzas at Bistro Nice cost 60 dollars.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of pizza at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "3 pieces of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine cost 2 dollars less than 2 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place. A Cobb salad at Mike's Place costs 14 dollars. 3 pieces of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 Cobb salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 48 dollars. Question: how much does a piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place, piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine, Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine are: 3 pieces of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine cost 2 dollars less than 2 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place, 3 pieces of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 Cobb salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 48 dollars.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of piece of fried chicken at Taste Good Cuisine."}
{"problem": "A scrambled egg at Texas BBQ and a creme brulee at Texas BBQ cost 18 dollars. A scrambled egg at Texas BBQ costs 3 dollars more than a creme brulee at Mike's Place. A scrambled egg at Texas BBQ costs 7 dollars less than 2 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place. Question: how much does a scrambled egg at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of scrambled egg at Texas BBQ, scrambled egg at Mike's Place, creme brulee at Texas BBQ, creme brulee at Mike's Place are: a scrambled egg at Texas BBQ costs 7 dollars less than 2 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place, a scrambled egg at Texas BBQ and a creme brulee at Texas BBQ cost 18 dollars, a scrambled egg at Texas BBQ costs 3 dollars more than a creme brulee at Mike's Place.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of scrambled egg at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "3 lasagnas at Mike's Place cost 4 dollars more than a lasagna at Bistro Nice. 2 pies at Mike's Place cost 9 dollars more than 3 lasagnas at Mike's Place. 3 pies at Mike's Place and 2 pies at Bistro Nice cost 56 dollars. Question: how much does a lasagna at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pie at Mike's Place, lasagna at Mike's Place, pie at Bistro Nice, lasagna at Bistro Nice are: 2 pies at Mike's Place cost 9 dollars more than 3 lasagnas at Mike's Place, 3 pies at Mike's Place and 2 pies at Bistro Nice cost 56 dollars, 3 lasagnas at Mike's Place cost 4 dollars more than a lasagna at Bistro Nice.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of lasagna at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "3 cream brulees at Texas BBQ and 3 pizzas at Mike's Place cost 48 dollars. A creme brulee at Texas BBQ costs 7 dollars. 2 pizzas at Texas BBQ and 3 cream brulees at Mike's Place cost 58 dollars. Question: how much does a creme brulee at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of pizza at Texas BBQ, creme brulee at Mike's Place are: 2 pizzas at Texas BBQ and 3 cream brulees at Mike's Place cost 58 dollars.\nThere are 2 variables but only 1 linear formula, so we cannot calculate the price of creme brulee at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "3 pieces of fried chicken at Bistro Nice and 2 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place cost 56 dollars. 2 pizzas at Bistro Nice cost a dollar less than a pizza at Mike's Place. A pizza at Bistro Nice costs 5 dollars. Question: how much does a piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice, piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place are: 3 pieces of fried chicken at Bistro Nice and 2 pieces of fried chicken at Mike's Place cost 56 dollars.\nThere are 2 variables but only 1 linear formula, so we cannot calculate the price of piece of fried chicken at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "A fruit tart at Mike's Place costs 12 dollars. A piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine costs 3 dollars less than a piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place. A fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine costs 2 dollars less than a piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine. Question: how much does a piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine, piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place, fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine are: a piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine costs 3 dollars less than a piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place, a fruit tart at Taste Good Cuisine costs 2 dollars less than a piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "3 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 87 dollars. 3 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 18 dollars less than 3 burgers at Mike's Place. A burger at Mike's Place costs 12 dollars. Question: how much does a BLT sandwich at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of burger at Taste Good Cuisine, BLT sandwich at Mike's Place are: 3 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 BLT sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 87 dollars.\nThere are 2 variables but only 1 linear formula, so we cannot calculate the price of BLT sandwich at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "A lasagna at Texas BBQ costs 13 dollars. 3 Caesar salads at Texas BBQ and 3 lasagnas at Mike's Place cost 63 dollars. The price of 3 Caesar salads at Mike's Place is the same as that of 3 Caesar salads at Texas BBQ. Question: how much does a Caesar salad at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Caesar salad at Texas BBQ, Caesar salad at Mike's Place, lasagna at Mike's Place are: the price of 3 Caesar salads at Mike's Place is the same as that of 3 Caesar salads at Texas BBQ, 3 Caesar salads at Texas BBQ and 3 lasagnas at Mike's Place cost 63 dollars.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Caesar salad at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "A grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine costs 7 dollars less than a BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine. 2 BLT sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 15 dollars less than 3 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine. A BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine costs 3 dollars less than 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ. Question: how much does a BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine, BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine, BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ, grilled cheese sandwich at Texas BBQ are: a grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine costs 7 dollars less than a BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine, 2 BLT sandwiches at Texas BBQ cost 15 dollars less than 3 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine, a BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine costs 3 dollars less than 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Texas BBQ.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine."}
{"problem": "3 fruit tarts at Urban Plate cost a dollar less than 2 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice. A fruit tart at Urban Plate and 3 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice cost 20 dollars. 2 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice and 2 Cobb salads at Urban Plate cost 30 dollars. Question: how much does a Cobb salad at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of fruit tart at Urban Plate, Cobb salad at Bistro Nice, fruit tart at Bistro Nice, Cobb salad at Urban Plate are: 3 fruit tarts at Urban Plate cost a dollar less than 2 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice, a fruit tart at Urban Plate and 3 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice cost 20 dollars, 2 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice and 2 Cobb salads at Urban Plate cost 30 dollars.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Cobb salad at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "A grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place costs 29 dollars less than 3 cream brulees at Mike's Place. A grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine costs 11 dollars less than 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Mike's Place. 2 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine cost 14 dollars more than a grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine. Question: how much does a grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine, grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place, creme brulee at Taste Good Cuisine, creme brulee at Mike's Place are: a grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine costs 11 dollars less than 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Mike's Place, 2 cream brulees at Taste Good Cuisine cost 14 dollars more than a grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine, a grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place costs 29 dollars less than 3 cream brulees at Mike's Place.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "3 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 15 dollars more than 3 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine. 3 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place cost 16 dollars more than 2 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine. 3 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine and a BLT sandwich at Mike's Place cost 42 dollars. Question: how much does a BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of scrambled egg at Mike's Place, BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine, BLT sandwich at Mike's Place, scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine are: 3 scrambled eggs at Mike's Place cost 16 dollars more than 2 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine, 3 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine and a BLT sandwich at Mike's Place cost 42 dollars, 3 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 15 dollars more than 3 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine."}
{"problem": "2 lasagnas at Bistro Nice cost 4 dollars less than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice. A lasagna at Taste Good Cuisine costs 10 dollars. A piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine costs 9 dollars less than 3 lasagnas at Bistro Nice. Question: how much does a piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of lasagna at Bistro Nice, piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine, piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice are: a piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine costs 9 dollars less than 3 lasagnas at Bistro Nice, 2 lasagnas at Bistro Nice cost 4 dollars less than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of piece of cheese cake at Taste Good Cuisine."}
{"problem": "3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Bistro Nice cost 13 dollars more than a grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate. 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 11 dollars less than 3 pieces of fried chicken at Bistro Nice. A piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice costs 29 dollars less than 3 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate. Question: how much does a grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice, grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate, piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice, piece of fried chicken at Urban Plate are: 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Bistro Nice cost 13 dollars more than a grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate, 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 11 dollars less than 3 pieces of fried chicken at Bistro Nice, a piece of fried chicken at Bistro Nice costs 29 dollars less than 3 pieces of fried chicken at Urban Plate.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "3 Cobb salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 15 dollars more than 3 Greek salads at Bistro Nice. A Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine costs 10 dollars. A Cobb salad at Bistro Nice costs 5 dollars less than 2 Greek salads at Bistro Nice. Question: how much does a Greek salad at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine, Greek salad at Bistro Nice, Cobb salad at Bistro Nice are: 3 Cobb salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 15 dollars more than 3 Greek salads at Bistro Nice, a Cobb salad at Bistro Nice costs 5 dollars less than 2 Greek salads at Bistro Nice.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Greek salad at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "3 burgers at Mike's Place and a Cobb salad at Mike's Place cost 43 dollars. 2 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice cost 10 dollars less than 3 burgers at Mike's Place. 2 burgers at Bistro Nice cost 8 dollars more than 2 burgers at Mike's Place. Question: how much does a Cobb salad at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of burger at Mike's Place, Cobb salad at Mike's Place, burger at Bistro Nice, Cobb salad at Bistro Nice are: 3 burgers at Mike's Place and a Cobb salad at Mike's Place cost 43 dollars, 2 burgers at Bistro Nice cost 8 dollars more than 2 burgers at Mike's Place, 2 Cobb salads at Bistro Nice cost 10 dollars less than 3 burgers at Mike's Place.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Cobb salad at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "A Greek salad at Urban Plate and 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 49 dollars. A Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine costs 15 dollars. 2 Greek salads at Urban Plate and 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 53 dollars. Question: how much does a grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Greek salad at Urban Plate, grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate, grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine are: 2 Greek salads at Urban Plate and 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 53 dollars, a Greek salad at Urban Plate and 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 49 dollars.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "A burger at Bistro Nice costs 12 dollars less than 3 fruit tarts at Mike's Place. 2 burgers at Mike's Place cost 11 dollars less than 3 fruit tarts at Mike's Place. A fruit tart at Bistro Nice costs 14 dollars less than 3 fruit tarts at Mike's Place. Question: how much does a burger at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of fruit tart at Mike's Place, burger at Mike's Place, burger at Bistro Nice, fruit tart at Bistro Nice are: 2 burgers at Mike's Place cost 11 dollars less than 3 fruit tarts at Mike's Place, a burger at Bistro Nice costs 12 dollars less than 3 fruit tarts at Mike's Place, a fruit tart at Bistro Nice costs 14 dollars less than 3 fruit tarts at Mike's Place.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of burger at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "A piece of cheese cake at Mike's Place costs 9 dollars. 3 lasagnas at Bistro Nice cost 27 dollars more than 2 pieces of cheese cake at Mike's Place. 3 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice and 3 lasagnas at Mike's Place cost 87 dollars. Question: how much does a lasagna at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice, lasagna at Mike's Place are: 3 pieces of cheese cake at Bistro Nice and 3 lasagnas at Mike's Place cost 87 dollars.\nThere are 2 variables but only 1 linear formula, so we cannot calculate the price of lasagna at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "2 cream brulees at Bistro Nice cost 9 dollars less than 3 cream brulees at Texas BBQ. 2 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ cost 9 dollars more than a piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice. 2 cream brulees at Bistro Nice cost 19 dollars more than a piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice. Question: how much does a piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice, piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ, creme brulee at Bistro Nice, creme brulee at Texas BBQ are: 2 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ cost 9 dollars more than a piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice, 2 cream brulees at Bistro Nice cost 19 dollars more than a piece of cheese cake at Bistro Nice, 2 cream brulees at Bistro Nice cost 9 dollars less than 3 cream brulees at Texas BBQ.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "3 burgers at Mike's Place and 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 28 dollars. 2 burgers at Mike's Place cost 4 dollars more than a burger at Taste Good Cuisine. 3 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 38 dollars. Question: how much does a grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of burger at Taste Good Cuisine, grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place, burger at Mike's Place, grilled cheese sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine are: 3 burgers at Taste Good Cuisine and 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Mike's Place cost 38 dollars, 2 burgers at Mike's Place cost 4 dollars more than a burger at Taste Good Cuisine, 3 burgers at Mike's Place and 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 28 dollars.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of grilled cheese sandwich at Mike's Place."}
{"problem": "The price of 3 pizzas at Texas BBQ is the same as that of 2 pizzas at Urban Plate. A BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ costs a dollar more than a pizza at Urban Plate. 3 pizzas at Urban Plate cost 20 dollars more than 2 BLT sandwiches at Urban Plate. Question: how much does a pizza at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ, pizza at Urban Plate, pizza at Texas BBQ, BLT sandwich at Urban Plate are: a BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ costs a dollar more than a pizza at Urban Plate, the price of 3 pizzas at Texas BBQ is the same as that of 2 pizzas at Urban Plate, 3 pizzas at Urban Plate cost 20 dollars more than 2 BLT sandwiches at Urban Plate.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of pizza at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "A BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ costs 14 dollars. 3 Greek salads at Texas BBQ and 2 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 43 dollars. 2 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 29 dollars less than 3 Greek salads at Taste Good Cuisine. Question: how much does a BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Greek salad at Texas BBQ, BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine, Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine are: 3 Greek salads at Texas BBQ and 2 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 43 dollars, 2 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 29 dollars less than 3 Greek salads at Taste Good Cuisine.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine."}
{"problem": "A Greek salad at Urban Plate costs 13 dollars. A Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine and a Cobb salad at Urban Plate cost 15 dollars. 3 Cobb salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 7 dollars less than 2 Greek salads at Taste Good Cuisine. Question: how much does a Cobb salad at Urban Plate cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine, Cobb salad at Urban Plate, Greek salad at Taste Good Cuisine are: a Cobb salad at Taste Good Cuisine and a Cobb salad at Urban Plate cost 15 dollars, 3 Cobb salads at Taste Good Cuisine cost 7 dollars less than 2 Greek salads at Taste Good Cuisine.\nThere are 3 variables but only 2 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of Cobb salad at Urban Plate."}
{"problem": "3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 12 dollars more than 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Bistro Nice. 2 lasagnas at Bistro Nice and 3 lasagnas at Urban Plate cost 65 dollars. 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Bistro Nice cost 7 dollars more than a lasagna at Bistro Nice. Question: how much does a grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of grilled cheese sandwich at Urban Plate, grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice, lasagna at Bistro Nice, lasagna at Urban Plate are: 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Urban Plate cost 12 dollars more than 3 grilled cheese sandwiches at Bistro Nice, 2 grilled cheese sandwiches at Bistro Nice cost 7 dollars more than a lasagna at Bistro Nice, 2 lasagnas at Bistro Nice and 3 lasagnas at Urban Plate cost 65 dollars.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of grilled cheese sandwich at Bistro Nice."}
{"problem": "3 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine and a BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ cost 34 dollars. A scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine costs 7 dollars less than a scrambled egg at Texas BBQ. 3 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 66 dollars. Question: how much does a BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine, BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ, BLT sandwich at Taste Good Cuisine, scrambled egg at Texas BBQ are: 3 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine and a BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ cost 34 dollars, 3 scrambled eggs at Taste Good Cuisine and 3 BLT sandwiches at Taste Good Cuisine cost 66 dollars, a scrambled egg at Taste Good Cuisine costs 7 dollars less than a scrambled egg at Texas BBQ.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of BLT sandwich at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "3 burgers at Texas BBQ cost 5 dollars less than 2 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ. 2 burgers at Bistro Nice cost 9 dollars more than a burger at Texas BBQ. 2 burgers at Bistro Nice cost 23 dollars less than 3 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice. Question: how much does a fruit tart at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of burger at Texas BBQ, fruit tart at Texas BBQ, burger at Bistro Nice, fruit tart at Bistro Nice are: 3 burgers at Texas BBQ cost 5 dollars less than 2 fruit tarts at Texas BBQ, 2 burgers at Bistro Nice cost 9 dollars more than a burger at Texas BBQ, 2 burgers at Bistro Nice cost 23 dollars less than 3 fruit tarts at Bistro Nice.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of fruit tart at Texas BBQ."}
{"problem": "3 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ cost 9 dollars more than 2 burgers at Texas BBQ. 3 burgers at Urban Plate cost 12 dollars more than 3 pieces of cheese cake at Urban Plate. 2 burgers at Texas BBQ and 2 pieces of cheese cake at Urban Plate cost 34 dollars. Question: how much does a piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ cost?", "answer": "unknown", "proof": "All we know about the prices of burger at Texas BBQ, piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ, piece of cheese cake at Urban Plate, burger at Urban Plate are: 3 pieces of cheese cake at Texas BBQ cost 9 dollars more than 2 burgers at Texas BBQ, 2 burgers at Texas BBQ and 2 pieces of cheese cake at Urban Plate cost 34 dollars, 3 burgers at Urban Plate cost 12 dollars more than 3 pieces of cheese cake at Urban Plate.\nThere are 4 variables but only 3 linear formulas, so we cannot calculate the price of piece of cheese cake at Texas BBQ."}
